One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
I can feel somebody waiting just out of sight, I'll see you soon
Slow your pace, this journey's not done, it's only begun
Bravery, friendship, and a bunch of love
And don't forget a little bit of playfulness
We'll treasure those feelings till we're gone
When we’re separated, something doesn’t feel right
(Separated…)
Like a puzzle missing pieces thrown off to the side
(We’re missing pieces…)
But just you wait, one day that puzzle will be whole
And when we come together, I can feel the wind blowing strong, YEAH!
Feel the wind, take it all in, you’ve gotta let the wind flow by
Should you feel your eyes welling up, you’ve gotta search out the wind, let it dry your tears
On a quest looking for friends, can’t wait to see how big our family gets
Nothing can stop this dream of mine
I can feel somebody waiting just out of sight, I’ll see you soon
Going back in time a bit, we find Zoro, who has
recently been sent to the same island as Perona...
Ruins of the Muggy Kingdom
Gloom Island
Is this...
...a tomb?
Who made this?!
It was carved from a massive tree.
Such incredible craftsmanship...
This thing is huge!
So fast!
What?! It got deflected!
H-Hey! Look!
You bastards!
The Land of Poverty, Hungeria
Lazy Bones Island
Meanwhile, on Lazy Bones Island
in the impoverished nation of Hungeria...
Brook was mistaken as
the Dark Lord, Satan, by its residents.
What a bright and beautiful morning!
It's the longarms!
Huh?
No!
Help me!
Do you wanna get hurt?!
Return that girl!
Quit messing with us, you bastards!
Let my daughter go!
We'll send you straight to hell!
Huh?!
No!
Help me!
You know they're abducting that young lady, right?
Yes!
Hurry up and hex them!
I beg you!
That's not– We need to save her! Now!
Lord Satan!
They took her...
I beseech you!
Please bring your wrath down upon them!
– We beseech you!
They're really dependent on other people!
But that young lady is a victim!
She doesn't deserve this!
All right!
I'll do it since I owe you for all the food...
Not to mention all the panties!
– Yeah!
– Satan!
– Satan! Satan!
Luffy. Everyone!
Right now, I have become Satan,
surrounded by panties.
My apologies, but...
could you wait a little longer?
I owe them a debt, and running off
without repaying it would be spineless!
So please, excuse my absence.
As soon as I complete this single task,
I'll be back by your side!
This is the Birdie Kingdom, in the South Blue,
where birds reign supreme.
Birdie Kingdom
South Blue
I really wanna get off this island.
This place is the worst.
The birds treat me like a toy.
The humans want to add me to their hot pot.
And what's more...
the birds and the humans...
are always fighting.
What should I do?
This is the Kamabakka Queendom
on Peachy Island, in the Grand Line.
Kamabakka Queendom
Peachy Island, Grand Line
What is this place?!
More importantly…
what's with these people?!
Damn!
I've been waiting for you!
Wh-Who are you?!
Dear Nami, Robin,
how are you both doing?
I'm looking forward to seeing you two!
When the time comes, I'm sure
that we'll become good friends!
This is the small sky island of Weatheria,
home to scientists who study the weather.
Weatheria
Young lady!
Over here!
A ship?!
Whoa! What's with this ship? It floats?!
Nooo!
Let's go!
What?!
This island is exactly what I was looking for!
This island?
You can save our island?!
Yes.
Just watch me use
weather science to make it rain!
What did you just say?!
Why, I could do it right now,
for the special price...
of 100 million belly!
100 million?!
Do you think that's a bit too much?
That's way too much! No one can afford that!
Is that so...?
Alright, then let's make it 100 belly!
Huh?!
– What a deal!
Are those...
soap bubbles?
There's something inside.
Young lady, could you generate
some wind with this?
Oh, this is...
Do you want it at full power?
Yes!
I can't believe this!
It's raining!
We did it!
They sure seem happy.
Yeah!
Now, don't you think that
weather science is useful?
Meanwhile, on Mech Island, Futureland: Baldimore,
the birthplace of a certain genius...
Mech Island
Futureland Baldimore
Let's get him to the hospital, Kitton!
Okay!
Surgery in
Progress
Ah, I see. He's a cyborg.
To think his energy source is cola…
What should we do?
We don't have any cola here.
There's no time to lose. Begin the operation.
Understood.
Surgery in
Progress
Mister!
Greetings! You're the young lad
from earlier, yes?
My apologies for keeping you waiting!
S-Something's different about you.
Indeed! Sadly, they don't
have any cola here, so...
they powered me up with tea instead.
It's Darjeeling!
Tea?
What a super flavour!
Now I feel super relaxed!
M-Mister!
Oh! How thoughtless of me!
There you are! Careful now, it's piping hot.
No, no! That's not what I was gonna say!
Mister! You were funnier before, and I miss it!
Oh, truly?
So cold!
How did I get here?
Splendid, a scarf!
Oh?
What is going on here?!
"Keep out"?
"This forest is a mecha-animal enclosure."
Operation: Surprise Jungle Awakening!
Survive and regain the wildness
in your heart, Mister!
Now, now, let's all calm down.
You all seem quite irritated.
Have you not eaten breakfast yet?
Your disposition will suffer
if you don't eat properly!
Ah, I see!
This is breakfast time!
What was I thinking?
Dee-licious!
Nothing quite like the first
cup of tea in the morning!
It feels great to be alive!
It's not working!
Help us!
Violence is not–
I know you're at the age where you want to act–
If you let me–
You'll see–
Let's sort this out...
in a civilized manner!
Stop...! Nothing good...
comes... from violence!
Mr. Frank!
Oh no, it's not working at all!
Relax–
Listen to what I–
Listen to what–
Listen to–
Listen–
Lis–
To–
Listen–
Lis–
Li–
Lis...
Super!
Who the hell do you think I am?!
I am the Franky!
Yeah!
You're back, Mister!
Per... vert!
What's the matter?
I got cooled down a little,
so I'm running out of steam!
That's a pervert! I mean, problem!
Um... Um...
Oh, yeah! Let me show you something!
Grandpa told me to keep away from here because
there are a lot of dangerous creations inside!
Tequila Wolf
East Blue
Here's your meal!
Once you finish, your
interrogation will continue!
Looking forward to it.
Sounds like you've been
hurt badly, young lady.
Who are you?
I'm just an old man.
I was sent to this country today,
but they said the elderly are useless
and put me in here.
I'm sorry to hear that.
What's that?!
Dissidents are running wild!
The warden ordered everyone
to go and break it up!
– Yes, sir!
Dissidents?
Yes, but as you ordered,
all units were dispatched
to calm the situation!
I didn't give that order.
Don't tell me that you even sent
the guards stationed at the tower!
I am an agent of the Revolutionary Army!
Imbecile!
I don't care about the dissidents!
Don't let Nico Robin get away!
Well done.
Under your command, victory is assured.
Worry not. You can count on me!
While you're at it,
free that young woman, too.
Shoot to kill!
Clutch!
You're Nico Robin?!
Bowin Archipelago
Grand Line
What the hell is this place?!
That smells delicious!
Oh yeah, these are definitely edible!
Ramenfalls!
Spaghetti patches!
Hamfruit!
And chocolate rocks for dessert!
You can eat whatever you see!
Oh, can I eat these?!
Go ahead'n.
Yum-yum!
If you eat a lot and build your stamina,
then the man-eating plants won't attack you'n!
Really? That's great!
These are really good!
I could eat them forever!
Don't just eat'n!
You need to work out, too!
I know!
But I need to eat a lot to become
a cool hero of the forest like you, right?
I can't eat another bite!
Usopp'n...
Fat things will surely be eaten on this island'n!
Surely be eaten?!
It is impossible to escape
from the Bowin Archipelago!
Impossible to escape?!
And I am the hero of the forest,
H–